{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649715356","data":{"timestamp":" 947649715355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649717393","data":{"timestamp":" 947649717392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649719316","data":{"timestamp":" 947649719316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649721535","data":{"timestamp":" 947649721535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649725103","data":{"timestamp":" 947649725103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649726790","data":{"timestamp":" 947649726790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649729505","data":{"timestamp":" 947649729505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649731620","data":{"timestamp":" 947649731620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649733348","data":{"timestamp":" 947649733348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649737390","data":{"timestamp":" 947649737390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649739842","data":{"timestamp":" 947649739842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649741759","data":{"timestamp":" 947649741759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649745788","data":{"timestamp":" 947649745788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649748000","data":{"timestamp":" 947649748000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649749908","data":{"timestamp":" 947649749907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649752219","data":{"timestamp":" 947649752219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649753978","data":{"timestamp":" 947649753977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649756131","data":{"timestamp":" 947649756131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649758920","data":{"timestamp":" 947649758920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649761424","data":{"timestamp":" 947649761424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649763265","data":{"timestamp":" 947649763265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649766013","data":{"timestamp":" 947649766011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649769240","data":{"timestamp":" 947649769240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649772300","data":{"timestamp":" 947649772300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649774208","data":{"timestamp":" 947649774207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649776203","data":{"timestamp":" 947649776202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649779137","data":{"timestamp":" 947649779136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649781989","data":{"timestamp":" 947649781988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649784560","data":{"timestamp":" 947649784559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649786757","data":{"timestamp":" 947649786756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649790673","data":{"timestamp":" 947649790672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649792701","data":{"timestamp":" 947649792700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649796085","data":{"timestamp":" 947649796085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649799111","data":{"timestamp":" 947649799111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649802240","data":{"timestamp":" 947649802240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649804305","data":{"timestamp":" 947649804304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649806778","data":{"timestamp":" 947649806778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649810186","data":{"timestamp":" 947649810186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649812097","data":{"timestamp":" 947649812096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649814237","data":{"timestamp":" 947649814237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649816627","data":{"timestamp":" 947649816626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649818657","data":{"timestamp":" 947649818657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649939257","data":{"timestamp":" 947649939257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649942603","data":{"timestamp":" 947649942602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649944871","data":{"timestamp":" 947649944870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649944979","data":{"timestamp":" 947649944978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 61c80b46-0fec-4eec-bea1-1a10f4255e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649953920","data":{"timestamp":" 947649953920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" d405aea6-588a-4bd1-872b-71bc85252164"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649954142","data":{"timestamp":" 947649954142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" d405aea6-588a-4bd1-872b-71bc85252164"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649955105","data":{"timestamp":" 947649955104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" d405aea6-588a-4bd1-872b-71bc85252164"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649955389","data":{"timestamp":" 947649955389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" d405aea6-588a-4bd1-872b-71bc85252164"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947649955470","data":{"timestamp":" 947649955470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" d405aea6-588a-4bd1-872b-71bc85252164"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650092564","data":{"timestamp":" 947650092564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650095986","data":{"timestamp":" 947650095986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650103248","data":{"timestamp":" 947650103248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650114163","data":{"timestamp":" 947650114163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650867310","data":{"timestamp":" 947650867310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650868621","data":{"timestamp":" 947650868621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650892622","data":{"timestamp":" 947650892622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650944739","data":{"timestamp":" 947650944739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650960041","data":{"timestamp":" 947650960041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650960044","data":{"timestamp":" 947650960043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650960465","data":{"timestamp":" 947650960465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651017698","data":{"timestamp":" 947651017698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651019522","data":{"timestamp":" 947651019522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651061754","data":{"timestamp":" 947651061754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651067029","data":{"timestamp":" 947651067029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651069774","data":{"timestamp":" 947651069774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651072385","data":{"timestamp":" 947651072385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651077089","data":{"timestamp":" 947651077089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" START_WALILIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651078974","data":{"timestamp":" 947651078973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_070144"," gameId":" 6889c649-a63f-44f8-9cc0-c79be99194a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" START_WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}